And have you taken it
for trading for a
long time? Please
advise me. If you look at the 6-month trade, the
stock has moved almost 30%.
Their outlook is also
for the long term. So, would it be
appropriate to keep this stock in your portfolio for a long-term return? It is a good
strategy
because this sector, which is
related to non-life general insurance
companies, looks good. If you
look at its history, I think its
performance from the time of its IPA till now, is probably very good.
It is also important to say that we do not have coverage,
so I will not comment specifically,
but we feel that this sector can
gradually become attractive.
[Music]
How do the results come and then how do the
valuations of those shares go up or
down. But one company in this sector
that we like is ICC
Lombard, and we have coverage on it. We have
recently set an upward trend.
After seeing the results, this company
can also do better, but it will depend on
how the results come. If we want to open a market, we
can do so. Should we
keep it for the long term?  This will be a
good decision,
Abhishek, I think its IPO
came around July 2021 and
I think it was around 880 to 950,
if you look from there, the
listing was good and after the listing
we saw that based on the results, the results were a little
weak, so on the downside,
we had a
rally for investing for the long term, so
it can remain, there is a
little
problem with the trend data, this
may be a little
problem with the small Modi, but Prashant Abhishek, our view on the entire
specialty agro chemical or chemical
sector,
sorry,
China plus one, Euro plus one, and just
two-three days ago, in my opinion, the entire chemical
sector was also there, but you should
give some time for this, if you do
not have any time limit, then you
can remain with a long term view,
and at present, the
quantity is also very high, much below their price, so the loss would be
huge because Sharma saheb,
tell me, how long can you hold the view, it is
okay
and there is also no problem with what you bought on the strength, that like this  The
price of crude oil is $90
per barrel. The price of crude oil is $
8688. If we compare it with our
Hanuman, then on the other hand, there are
state level elections in our country next year, a very
big election. The oil marketing companies may have to
suffer some losses if the government takes some decisions
regarding the policies of the state level and
if the central government takes some decisions, then
recently we saw that there was some problem
regarding the price of gas cylinders
and if KK Sharma ji has a
year or a little
more time instead of 6 months, he can extend his investment
if time is not bothering him much
and if he has a time limit, then
in my opinion, first of all our disclosure is
that we have a purchase opinion and Prashant is saying that the
investment opinion given by these three oil marketing companies regarding green hydrogen and the way
this entire process of green nitrogen will
move forward, then in my opinion, it can bring a
big change. The
problem for the oil marketing companies is this,
plus the reduction of 5 lakh barrels per
day in the country.  There was
talk of further increase in crude oil prices, due to which this is being seen as a fraud. On
the other hand, the rupee has also reached 83 against
$1, so
you may be a little worried in the short term,
but if you have time, we would advise you to stay here. I had
withdrawn your shares here for longevity because of the kind of
news that came about this company and
also looked at a lot of downside risks. Stocks,
mostly, I think there is
relief in the film's building period, but now since you are not here, I will
not be able to comment on a specific topic.
But we have some other choices in this sector, for
example, Link Housing
Finance, Repco Home Finance,
or Kenfil Housing. According to us,
if you measure based on fundamentals, then
these companies or the three names I have mentioned,
more importantly, based on the results, can be
an excellent investment suggestion for you. I am
not in the compact market at the moment, so I will
not be able to comment specifically. If you can make
changes, then making changes would be
appropriate in my opinion.
Congratulations, you are getting a good profit,
1250 shares profit.  See, 25350
double engine and triple engine can be built here
and the impact disclosure will be made whenever it happens.
Abhishek, we had an investment rally in IFSC and I believe that in the
last two-three days, if we
look at the dare from the top side, then a little bit of profit has been
affected by the inflation but for the long term, it will be made
directly and the image of Indian Railways is
improving, it is on the basis of the whole nation, from
here, there can be a better trend with regard to the data,
so for the long
term, I would advise to stay with Nivedita
because we have given long term subscription in IPO,
if we look at the sugar sector, if
we look at sugar stocks, then there is any particular thing here which
seems attractive to you,
Prashant Bhai, I will
not be able to give a company specific answer to your question because there is
no coverage, but I will try to easily present this entire perspective to your
viewers and investors
and just like your colleague was telling that the
states of Maharashtra and Karnataka are
very high producers
and I made this comment in the beginning that there is
some concern regarding rain in the
market, inflation is going up here.
So when there is less production of sugar, it is
natural that the production of sugar will also
decrease.
I think there is a huge difference between the production of sugar and the production of sugar. There are many
concerns regarding the date. Now if there is less production of sugar,
then the production will decrease and then the
production of ethanol will also decrease
because so much like by-product is produced
when you make sugar. There
can be these two benefits in the sugar sector, firstly regarding ethanol
and all those where there is
discrimination in the price of sugar
and sugar, if the
difference in the price reduces a little, then
we can also say one thing that
you can keep an eye on the capable and strong companies in this sector. At
one time, Prashant, we had coverage
on Balrampur Sugar a long time ago, but
after achieving our target, we have removed that coverage. The
government is also making a big effort regarding the marketing of ethanol, which will be done
with the marketing companies,
due to which I think the consumption of
ethanol will also be reduced.  It will be higher and
we have also seen upward trends in the prices of ethanol per liter.
Okay, so this is the view of sugar companies. But
look at today, Balrampur Chini is up by 2% and
we are seeing good growth in other sugar companies as well. The
reason is that there is a little fear right now. Let me
tell you the auspicious time beforehand. Let's keep bringing out these companies in the
future as well.
But
you had taken this for the long term.
You had taken it at 27. RVNL
is good and you entered at such a good level,
see, you got the benefit of it too. RVNL was
taken at 27 rupees, it has reached 150.
Look at MMTC also, it was taken at 42 rupees. In the last
three years, the growth in both the government companies was
good. MMTC has gone up by about 50% in the
meantime and even today it is trading 6% higher.
Gaurang, how is MMTC doing? You have
seen a great growth in the company. At
present, it should still stay here. It is making very
good profits too. Would you
advise them to stay here or exit with profits?
And in my opinion, the stock is above 65 percent, so
if you  If you look at it from the perspective of
Pooja, you are making a good profit,
and you invest in the stock market
because you want to make a profit, that
means cleaning it also becomes very expensive.
When you make a profit, we suggest
that you should continuously accumulate profits. It
depends on your thinking when you invested
in that company, what percentage of
profit you will get. So, let me give you a
very simple example of a bank.
Pooja, if you keep your money in a bank HD,
you get a return of 7% or 7%.
If you consider inflation, fear of inflation, and taxes,
then that return becomes very
meager. If
you get a return of 15-20, 25% in the stock market, then
you should continuously divide and accumulate profits.
We are not saying that you should take the entire profit,
but you should consider at least 30-40% profit.
Now, coming to MMTC, there is
no specific coverage here, so
I cannot specifically advise on buying, holding,
or buying the stock.
But yes, as I have commented,
if the profits are good, then
you should continuously accumulate profits, be it in any sector of the company.
You should continuously accumulate profits in it.
If you want an option, then as an
option, there is a small private sector
bank which has
performed very well and we have
discussed it earlier also, that is IDFC First
Bank, so this is an option in the form of change.
What is the matter with
Jio Finance and today is a very important day and
Abhishek, first of all, this entire demerger happened
and a
special
17 was kept
there for value discovery and
I think the book value of Jio Financial Services is around
261. I think that value discovery close of 6, 5, 8, 5 came at the
time, then
Jio Financial Services got
listed and then there was continuous Gwalior,
in a very big market, there were continuous
downward circuits of 5% and the stock
hit around 210, only then
I think some
promoter
entities might have made some purchases, there were some such
reports also. Now the problem is that the
clarification given by Mukesh Ambani ji
regarding Jio Financial Services is unknown, he
wants to go into asset management company, wants to go
into insurance, wants to
go into micro finance, power ahead.  I started
eating it, it means that right now
we do not have any such system to give advice on
buying, selling or
holding on to the criteria based on the basic star because whatever they
want to enter into business, it may take
time to start work on Gemini Star
because
you will have to take permissions formally from all the sides and only after that work can
start and when this company
was under the balance sheet of Reliance, then we had
a strong buying opinion
on Reliance Industries even then and it is still there today, now it is difficult for
Abhishek because we do not have any data star,
so we will
not be able to comment specifically,
I have a lion
and I took it in 1475 and I
took it in this team that this new technology is
engaged in cognition etc.
and these three were in science etc. so madam it is
not a question of money, it just wants to make more hits
but it is not being caught with me,
first of all let me give the disclosure, Pooja
its IPO came in March 2021 and
Sarthak was around 575,
we had a lot of it on time  We had
discussed this in the big IPO
and we had given our advice for investment for the
long term. The meaning of subscribe comment was
eating.
Ramesh ji, I would like to tell you one thing, first of all,
you should never feel sad after investing in the stock market
when the stock
goes up because then you will
not be able to enjoy it.
You had to invest more and the stock ran away. The
reason for its success is Chandrayaan and Aditya
album
which were launched by ISRO and their success was
quite successful. Please
help ISRO in this regard and
this company is very expert in space science and nuclear science
and moving forward at a very fast pace,
they can get orders.
I was listening to the statement of their management.
I think 2003 days ago on Monday,
its management was giving some statement
regarding the future of the business and the
way the government is encouraging
nuclear science space. There is no
listed entity in the stock market to compare it, that is,
its comparison, that is, by-by-by comparison,
you cannot do it. If you had to invest, then
our opinion would be that if you have
enough time frame and your perspective is 3
years  If it is for 5 years, then every month whatever
you have investment amount, be it 5
shares, 10 shares, 15 shares, whatever you want to add, you can
add it every month and if you
keep an eye on three to five years, then
after completion of this time period, the shares you will have in the mantra
and the way this company will
spend less, based on that the figures will come
and on that basis the strength of the shares will be,
you will be surprised that you have
invested so successfully.